http://www.baytownsun.com/site/terms/terms.html

Terms
Southern Newspapers Inc., owner of The Baytown Sun and www. baytownsun.com, is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using our web site and related online services.This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit or subscribe to the site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any personal information received by Southern Newspapers Inc. in connection with your subscriptions to the print edition of The Baytown Sun.We may make content or services from other Web sites partnered with The Baytown Sun available to you from links located on www. baytownsun.com. These other sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such site to determine how that site protects your privacy.Information we collectGeneral: When you register, and at other times, we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, age, address, e-mail address, credit-card number and facts about your computers, profession, investing habits and similar information. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.Web Site Usage Information: We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit the site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our sites, including the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each page, and the length of their visits.How we use information collectedWe may use information in the following ways:For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions or registrations.To send you notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.We may combine the information that we collect from you on the site with information that you provide to us in connection with your use of our other products, services and sites.Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of Southern Newspapers Inc. unless you "opt in" to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us.Compliance with legal processWe may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to(1) comply with the law or with legal process;(2) protect and defend our rights and property;(3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web sites; or(4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Subscriber Agreement or Terms of Use (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights).Online advertisingWhen you view an ad, our third-party advertising company may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The information collected is not personally identifiable and is used only to track response to our advertising efforts.Comments and questionsIf you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at support@baytownsun.com.
ProFootball UPickem
Today's e-Edition
Thursday
To view our latest e-Edition click the image on the left.
Greater Baytown
Greater Baytown - November 2020
To view our latest e-Edition click the image on the left.
Chambers County Weekly
Chambers County Weekly
To view our latest issue click the image on the left.
Obituaries
Quinton H. McDaniel Jr.
Updated
Dec 9, 2020
Juanita Genoveva Flores
Dec 9, 2020
Mac Hudman
Dec 9, 2020
Sun Weekly Survey
While lawmakers need to pass a stopgap spending bill to keep the government running, how important is it to you that they approve more spending for Covid-19 relief?
You voted:
Very important
Somewhat important
Neither important or unimportant
Somewhat unimportant
Very unimportant
I don't care
Vote
View Results
Back
Sign Up For Newsletters
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
News Updates
Would you like to receive our daily news? Signup today!
Manage your lists
Latest News
GC ceremony heralds school construction
CCSO: Man takes own life in Winnie standoff
Lee College to host free COVID-19 testing
Council to weigh diamond-grinding phase of work on North Main
Early voting ends with over 1,000 ballots cast
Safety driving wider Wallisville intersections
Tradition-laden REL ends drought
Popular tailor, adopted Baytonian passes at 70
Popular BaytownSun Stories
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesBPD: Robbers kill man in home invasionRemembering PVILCA Hall of Famer - Kenneth M. WilsonLuis Antonio GonzalezRonald Lee MarshMonroe Nichols, Jr. - PVILCA Hall of Famer dies at age 81Man succumbs to gunshot woundsKenneth M. WilsonAnswers still sought in death of UIW studentChristmas on Texas Avenue: ‘Haven’t seen this good a turnout in a long time’Bill L. Farmer
Images
VideosSorry, there are no recent results for popular videos.
CommentedTrump is the loser (7)Gas-lighting alert (3)Election fraud cries just a scam (2)Never say die (2)Wear your mask, please (1)The ride ahead ... (1)Vote for Parent and Lester (1)The Architects: Hope returns to Baytown football (1)What do you think about the outcome of the presidential election? (1)The election is over (1)
Letters to the Editor
No liberals on council
23 hrs ago
Powell deserves vote
23 hrs ago
Vote for Cummings
23 hrs ago
Cummings is change agent Baytown needs
Call 281-422-8302 or email david.bloom@baytownsun.com to wish someone a happy birthday. We will print your birthday wish on Page 2 of The Sun.
Happy Birthday Wishes
Top Ads
GCCISD is accepting proposals from qualified vendors in response to
© Copyright 2020 Baytown Sun, 1301 Memorial Drive Baytown, TX | Terms of Use
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
